3tailer.com 2013-03-09

# On Sale: Privacy Policy - Discount Cheap

**Sign up for our newsletter**   
_be the first to learn of new sale events and coupons!_

## Your privacy is important to us.

**Here at 3tailer we are committed to protecting your privacy.** We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully. We collect information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best service possible.

We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent by signing up for our newsletter. We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us.

The type of information we may securely collect about you includes:

  * \- Name
  * \- Email Address
  * \- Physical Address
  * \- Phone Number
  * \- Credit/Debit Card Details

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly. The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

We may share your information with service providers for specific business purposes such as facilitating the processing of your order or for answering your inquiry.  The information we collect from you may be shared with our trusted marketing partners or other trusted third parties. We may use the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other trusted third parties to bring selected retail opportunities to you via direct mail, email and/or telemarketing.

We also send newsletters to users if they have agreed to receive this mailing. If you would like to stop receiving newsletters please contact us at the “contact us” link at the bottom of this privacy policy.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. None of this information will ever be given out or sold in any way, shape, or form.

From time to time we may update this privacy policy. If we change this policy in a way that materially changes the use of your information we will notify you by a notice on our site.

**All cient information is transferred securely using a better than industry standard Verisign 256-bit Extended Valdiation Certificate.  Verify below:**

If you have any questions/comments about your privacy, you should contact us.
